{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":180,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":2,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_201","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25601","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si25497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Welsome to the CSAM Matching Game Match the phishing term with its definition ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25508","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si25528","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25532","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25549","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25553","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Smishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25570","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Search Engine Phishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25750","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25754","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Spear Phishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25768","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25772","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Whaling ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25786","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25790","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Catphishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25519","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si25538","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25542","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Not random, targeging a specific person ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25542ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Not random, targeging a specific person","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si25559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25563","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Targets ‘C’ titles (CISO, CFO, CEO, etc.) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25563ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Targets ‘C’ titles (CISO, CFO, CEO, etc.)","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si25580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25584","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Over phone - voice+ phishing   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25584ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Over phone - voice+ phishing  ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si25798","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Targets dating sites and social media ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25802ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Targets dating sites and social media","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si25809","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Using SMS (texting) alerts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25813ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Using SMS (texting) alerts","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si25820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25824","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Creates a fake webpage ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25824ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Creates a fake webpage","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si25609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25626","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25639","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25651","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25681","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25693","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25710","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25444q0","for":"Slide25444q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25597","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25444","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_201","SmartShape_11","si25497","si25542","si25563","si25584","si25802","si25813","si25824","si25609","si25626","si25639","si25651","si25668","si25681","si25693","si25710","si25723","si25597"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25444"},"question":{"interactionId":"25460","quizId":458,"title":"Matching","text":"Welsome to the CSAM Matching Game\rMatch the phishing term with its definition\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_202","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_202","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"CSAM Match Game","class":"project","title":"CSAM Match Game","children":["Slide25444","Slide6038"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide25444q0"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":10,"passScore":8}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide25444","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 2"}]}